#### Yair Zimmerman

050-4204700 <u>yyairzi22@gmail.com</u> South District.

I have extensive knowledge in computers, experience in sales and a developed technical sense. Furthermore, I am dedicated, determined, a fast learner and an excellent communicator.

Languages: Native Hebrew, Conversational English

.

### **Work Experience:**

# 2023- 2024- IT manager - Katz Group Itd

- Overseeing Katz Group's computer system, network, IT procurement, and policies.
- Integrating and training of employees on computing, software and data protection.

# 2017- 2022 IT and Information Systems Coordinator, Maccabi Health Fund

- Point person for technical errors. Responsible for computer maintenance, collaboration and integration in the Southern District of Maccabi
- Specification and adaptation of new Maccabi computer programs for the benefit of the district
- Responsible for execution of data security projects

# 2012-2017: Clinic Administrator, Sela Center

- Administrator in a center for treatment, counseling and guidance for drug victims.
- Interfaced with a variety of private and government agencies

## 2007-2012: Senior Sales and Consulting Representative, Bezeg

- Sales representative for a wide range of home and business equipment
- Responsible for the referral and control center of the sales department in the Jerusalem area.
- Met defined sales targets on a regular basis

## 2006-2007: Senior Customer Success Representative, Bezeq

- Customer success and retention in the private business sector
- · Met defined sales targets and retention of customers.

### 2004-2006: Customer Success Representative, Bezeg

- Met sales targets and retained regular customers
- Provided courteous, efficient and patient service
- Following two years in this position was promoted to the position of senior representative

## **Education:**

2016-2017: MCSA + CCNA course studies, NESS College Beer Sheva

Skills: Win OS, AD, 365, VMware, Saas Softwares, Priority, networks and Great technical knowledge.

# **Military Service:**

2001-2003: Service in the Armored Corps, 188th Brigade

## **Volunteer Experience**

Senior Medic and Ambulance Driver, Magen David Adom